University of Illinois Collection of Police Agreements and Arbitration Files 6334
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Fitchburg, MA - Battle Creek, MI (Box 8)
  - Lawrence, MA 7/78-6/80, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Leominster, MA 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Lexington, MA 5 agreements 74-83, 1974-1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lowell, MA 1 agreement 1/75-12/76, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lynn, MA 1 agreement 7/75-6/77, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Malden, MA 1 agreement 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Malden, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/78-6/80, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Medford, MA 4 agreements 1/73-6/74; 7/75-6/80, 1973-1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Methuen, Massachusetts 3 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Milton, MA 1 agreement. 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Natick, MA 1 agreement. 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Needham, Massachusetts 7 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - New Bedford, Massachusetts 3 agreements 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - New Bedford, MA 2 arbitration Ands 1977;1980 1 atty. Gen. opinion 1 sup. Ct. Decsn. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Newton, MA 2 agreements 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Northampton, MA 7/77-6/79 (1 agreement), 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Norwood, Massachusetts 4 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Pittsfield, MA 2 agreements 7/76-6/80, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Plymouth, MA 2 agreements 7/76-6/79, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Plymouth, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/79-6/81, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Quincy, MA 1 agreement 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Quincy, MA 1 arbitration award. 7/78-6/81, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Revere, Massachusetts 3 agreements. 1974-81 (2 are estd. In encd. arbitration awards.), 1974-1981 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Salem, MA 1 agreement 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Saugus, MA 2 agreements 7/77-6/82, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Somerville, MA 1 agreement 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Springfield, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/77-6/80, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Springfield, Massachusetts 1 agreement. 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Stoughton, MA 2 agreements 7/78-6/82, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Taunton, MA 2 agreements 7/78-6/82, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Taunton, MA 1 arbitration award for 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Wakefield, Massachusetts 4 agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Waltham, MA 5(4 agreements 74-82), 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Watertown, MA 1 arbitration And 2 FF Reports 1976; 1979 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Watertown, Massachusetts 3 agreements 76-82, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Wellesley, Massachusetts 3 agreements 1975-1978, 1980-1982, 1975-1982 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Westfield, MA 1 agreement 7/79-6/81, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Wermouth, MA2 agreements 7/77-6/82, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Woburn, MA 1 agreement 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Worcester, MA 1 arbitration award. 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Worcester, MA 3 agreements 73-81, 1973-1981 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Allen Park, MI 4 agreements 7/74-6/82, 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Allen Park, MI 1 arbitration Award spursy Officers 7/80-6/83, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Ann arbitrationor, MI 4 agreements 1970-74; 1976-81, 1970-1981 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Battle Creek, MI 2 agreements 1973-78, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Bay City, MI - Midland, MI (Box 9)
  - Bay City, MI 1 arbitration award. 7/74-6/76, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bay City, Michigan 3 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Burton, Michigan 1 arbitration award. 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Burton, Michigan (1 agreement 79-82), 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Detroit, MI 5 arbitration Awards 70/71-72/72-73 73-77 + 77-80 agreements, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Detroit, Michigan 4 agreements 1973-83, 1973-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Farminghouse Hills, Michigan 6 agreements 3 patrolmen 1972-75: 1977-81 3 sgt+lt. 1975-84, 1972-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Farmington Hills, MI 1 arbitration award. 1981 7/75-6/78, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Flint, Michigan 2 agreements 1975-80 see arbitration File 1980-83, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Flint, MI 3 arbitration awards for 80-83 78-79 agreements, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Grand Rapids, Michigan 3 agreements 1974-1982 period (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Grand Rapids, MI 2 arbitration awards 1977; 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Grosse Pointe Woods 1 arbitration Award 7/73-6/75, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Grosse Pointe Woods 2 agreements 7/75-6/78, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Holland, MI 1 agreement 1979-82, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Inkster, Michigan 2 agreements 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Inkster, MI 1 arbitration award. Supervisor 1975 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Jackson, MI 1 arbitration award. 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Jackson, MI 2 agreements 76-82, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Kalamazoo, MI 2 awards 1/75-12/76, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Kalamazoo, MI 1 agreement 81-83, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lansing, Michigan 3 agreements 3 arbitration awards 1972-74/ 1976-78/ 1978-80, 1972-1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lansing, MI 3 arbitration awards. --see contract file--, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Lincoln Park, MI 4 arbitration awards 7/72-6/73 7/78-6/81 7/81-6/83, 1972-1983 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Lincoln Park, MI 1 agreement --command 78-81, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Liuonia, MI 1 arbitration Award 2/73-11/76, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Livonia, MI 1 agreement 1979-82, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Madison Heights, Michigan 2 contracts 1979-81, 1981-82, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Midland, MI 2 awards 7/70-6/71, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Midland, MI - Brooklyn, MN (Box 10)
  - Midland, MI 3agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Muskegon, MI 1 arbitration award. 1/73-12/73, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Muskegon, Michigan 3 agreements 76-81, 1976-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pontiac, Michigan 5 agreements 3 police officer 1974-81 2 police spusr 1976-81, 1974-1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pontiac, MI 1 arbitration award. 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Port Huron, Michigan 5 agreements 4 officers 73-83 1 sgt.+lts 80-83, 1973-1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Port Huron, MI 1 arbitration award. 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Roseville, Michigan 4 agreements 73-83 1 extra copy 81-83-agreement, 1973-1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Roseville, MI 1 arbitration award. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Southfield, MI 1 arbitration Award. 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Sterling Heights, MI 1. arbitration award. -- command officers, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sterling Heights, Michigan 2 agreements: patrol officers 1980-82 1 command officer 1980-82, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Trenton, MI 1 arbitration award. 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Trenton, Michigan 4 agreements 1967-69 1975-81 and 1 lts. agreement 75-78, 1967-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Troy, Michigan 3 patrol Offer. agreements. 3 sgt. + lt agreements. (follow pl 1976-82) and 4 extra copies of agreements., 1973- 1982 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Warren, MI 4 agreements. 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Warren, MI 1 arbitration award. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Wyandotte, MI 2 agreements 1978-81, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Wyoming, Michigan 3 agreement 1974-84, 1974-1984 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Wyoming, MI 1. arbitration award 7/79-7/80, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Austin, Mn 4 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Austin, MN 1 arbitration award. 1979 (+ 1 griev. arbitration award. --) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Blaine, Minnesota 2 arbitration awards 1975; 1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Blaine, Minnesota 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Bloomington, Minnesota 70 agreements period 4 police ofcrs 1974-82 3 spusr agreements 1975-79 1 extra copy of ofcr agreement 79-80, 1974-1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Brooklyn Center, Mn. 4 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Brooklyn Center, MN - Belleville, NJ (Box 11)
  - Brooklyn Center, Mn. 1 arbitration award. 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Park, Minnesota 1 agreement 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Burnsville, Mn. 1 agreement 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Burnsville, Mn. 2 arbitration Awards for 1/77-12/77 1/82-12/83, 1977-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Coon Rapids, Minnesota 5 agreements 1975-82 period, 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Crystal, Mn., 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Duluth, Mn. 3 arbitration Awards for 1/74-12/74 1/77-12/78 1/81-12/82, 1974-1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Duluth, Mn. 1 agreement. 1/79-12/80, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Edina, Mn. 1 arbitration Award 1/76-12/77, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Mankato, Mn. 2 arbitration awards. OK 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mankato, Minnesota 5 agreements; 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Maplewood, Mn. 1 arbitration Award 1/75-12/75, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Minneapolis, Mn. 1 arbitration award-- for 81-82 agreement, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Minnetonka, Mn. 4 agreements 1975-80, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Minnetonka, Mn. 1 arbitration award. 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Moorhead, Minnesota 6 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Moorhead, Mn. 2 arbitration awards 1980; 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Plymouth, Minnesota 4 agreements; 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Plymouth, Mn. 1 arbitration award. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Richfield, Mn. 4 agreements 75-81, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Rochester, Minnesota 5 agreements 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Rochester, Mn. 1 arbitration Award 1/82-12/83, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Roseville, Mn 2 arbitration awards 1975; 1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Roseville, Minnesota 5 agreements 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - St. Cloud, Mn. 1 arbitration award 1/80-12/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - St. Louis Park, Mn. 2 arbitration awards 75, 78, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - St. Louis Park, Mn. 4 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - St Paul., Mn 3 arbitration awards --1974, 1975-- 1979, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - St. Paul, Minnesota 5 agreements 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Winona, Minnesota 1 agreement 1982 cal. Yr. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Billings, Montana 3 agreements 1977-82, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Butte. - Silver Bow, Montana 1 Sheriff's Deputy agreement 75-77 3 police agreements 75-76; 78-81, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Great Falls, MT 4 agreements 74-82, 1974-1982 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Helena, MT agreement 80-82, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Missoula, Montana 4 agreements 1977-83, 1977-1983 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Missoula, Montana 1 arbitration award 1981 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Lincoln, Nebraska 3 agreements 1977-83, 1977-1983 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Lincoln, Nebraska 1 ruling of NE Commission of IR 1 copy of rules of NE CIR, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Carson City, Nevada 5(2 agreements 1977-82 period), 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - North Las Vegas, Nevada, 1977-1983 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Reno, Nevada 80 agreements Police Nonsupervisory supervisory, 1974-1983 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Sparks, Nevada 8 agreements 1973-1982 period (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Nashua, NH 2 agreements 78-84, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Atlantic City, NJ, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Atlantic City, NJ, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Bayonne, NJ, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Bayonne, NJ 2 arbitration Awards 1-80-12/80 1/81-12/82, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Belleville, NJ 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Belleville, NJ 3 arbitration awards. 76, 77, 81, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Bergen County, NJ - Lodi, NJ (Box 12)
  - Bergen County, NJ 2 agreements 1978-82, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bergenfield, NJ, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bloomfield Twp, NJ (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brick Twp. New Jersey 5 agreements 1974-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Brock Twp, NJ 1 arbitration award. 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bridgewater Twp, NJ 1 arbitration award 1/79-12/81, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bridgewater, Twp, NJ., 1974-1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Camden, NJ 4 agreements 1971-81, 1971-1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Camden, NJ 1 arbitration award 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cherry Hill, NJ, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cherry Hill. NJ 1 arbitration Award 1/79-12/79, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Clifton, NJ 3 agreements 78-82, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dover Twp, NJ 3 agreements 1976-81, 1976-1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Dover Twp, NJ 2 arbitration awards 1/80-12/81 1/82-12/83, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - East Brunswick, NJ 4 agreements 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - East Orange, NJ, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Elizabeth, NJ 2 arbitration awards. 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth, NJ 4 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Ewing Twp, NJ, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Fair Lawn Brough, NJ (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Fort Lee, NJ 1 award 1/78-12/79, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Franklin Twp, NJ, 1976-1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Franklin Twp, NJ, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Garfield, NJ arbitration awards 1/80-12/80 1/81-12/82, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Gloucester Twp, NJ 1 award 1/79-12/79, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Hackensack, NJ, 1976-1983 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Hackensack, NJ 1 award. 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Hamilton Twp. New Jersey 4 agreements 1/75-12-82, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Hoboken, New Jersey 4 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Hoboken, New Jersey 2 arbitration awards -- 1980; 1981 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Irvington, NJ 2 arbitration awards. 1978; 1981, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Jersey City, New Jersey 4 contracts POBA 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Jersey City, New Jersey 2 arbitration awards. 1978-80 POOBA 1979 Superior Ofers 11 griev arbitration awads + ff rpts, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Kearny, NJ 1 arbitration award. 1979 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Lakewood, NJ 5 agreement 76-84, 1976-1984 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Lakewood, Twp, NJ 2 arbitration awards 1/79-12/79 1/81-12/81, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Linden, NJ 1 award 1/78-12/78, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Linden, NJ, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Livingston Twp, NJ, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Lodi, NJ 2 agents 77-79, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Lodi, NJ 2 arbitration awards. 1/80-12/80, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Long Branch, NJ - Woodbridge Twp, NJ (Box 13)
  - Long Branch, NJ 1 agreement 80-81, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Long Branch, NJ 1 award. 1/80-12/81, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Millville, NJ 1 arbitration award 1/80-12/80, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Millville, NJ, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Montclair, NJ, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Montclair, NJ, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New Brunswick, NJ 1 arbitration Award 1/78-12/79, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New Brunswick, NJ, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Newark, NJ, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Newark, NJ 2 offers award 1 superior ofcrs. Award, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - North Bergin, NJ 1 award 1/80-12/81, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Nutley, NJ 2 awards 1/78-12/78, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Old Bridge Twp, NJ 4 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Orange, NJ, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Paramus, NJ, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Paramus, NJ 1 award 1/79-12/80, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Passaoc, NJ, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Passaic, NJ, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Pennsauken Twp, NJ, 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Perth Amboy, NJ, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Piscataway, New Jersey 6 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Piscataway, New Jersey arbitration award 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Plainfield, NJ 8 agreements 1969-81, 1969-1981 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Plainfield, NJ 1 award 1/78-12/79, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Rahway, New Jersey (2 agreements 1978-82), 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Ridgewood, NJ, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Sayreville, New Jersey 3 agreements 1975-79, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Sayreville, New Jersey 2 arbitration awards. 80;81, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Teaneck, New Jersey 3 agreements 1978-82, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Teaneck, New Jersey 1 arbitration award 1979 1 award 1/78-12/78, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Union City, NJ 2 arbitration Award 2 arbitration. Award 1/79-12/80 1/81-12/82, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Union City, NJ, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Union Twp, New Jersey 2 patrol ofcr agents 79-82, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Vineland, NJ, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Vineland, NJ 1 award 1/81-12/83, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Wayne, New Jersey 3 agreements 75-81, 1975-1981 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Wayne, NJ 1 arbitration award 1981 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - West New York, NJ, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - West New York, NJ 3 awards, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - West Orange, NJ 1 award 1/78-12/78, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Westfield, New Jersey 5 agents 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Willingboro, NJ, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Willingboro, NJ 1 award 1/79-12/80, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Woodbridge Twp NJ 2 agreements 1978-82, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Woodbridge Twp, NJ - Poughkeepsie, NY (Box 14)
  - Woodbridge Twp, NJ 1 arbitration award 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Albuquerque, NM 5 agreements 1973-82, 1973-1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Albany, NY arbitration award. 1976 on pp 29-30 of 76-78 agreement in contract file (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Albany, NY 3 agreements 1976-78; 1979-81, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Amsterdam, NY 1 arbitration award for 1/74-12/75, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Amsterdam, NY 3 agreements 1/76-12/81, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Auburn, NY 1 arbitration Award for 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Auburn, NY 1 agreement 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo, New York 3 arbitration awards for 75-76 76-78 agreements 80-82, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo, New York 1 agreement 1978-80 see, arbitration File for award that contains 1980-82 contract, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Elmira, New York 1 arbitration award for 81+82 agreement, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Elmira, New York 3 agreements 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Freeport, NY 1 arbitration Award for 3/75-2/76, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Freeport, New York 1 agreement 1981-83 2 copies, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Garden City, NY 2 arbitration awards. 1975; 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Garden City, NY 4 agreements 1975-85, 1975-1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Glen Cove, NY 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hempstead, NY 2 agreements 6/76-5/77, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Ithaca, NY 2 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Jamestown, New York 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Kingston, NY 4 agreements 1974-77 1980-82, 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Kingston, NY 1 award 1/76-12/76, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Lackawanna, NY 3 arbitration awards 1/75-12/76 1/79-12/80, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Lackawanna, NY 1 agreement 1/79-12/80, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Lockport, NY 6 agreements (1973-81), 1973-1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Long Beach, NY 2 arbitration Awards 7/79-6/81 7/81-6/83, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Long Beach, NY 1 agreement with addenda wage changes 7/79-6/83, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Middletown, New York 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Mt. Vernon, NY 2 agreement 1/77-12/77 1/78-12/79, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Middletown, NY 1 arbitration award 1977 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Mt. Vernon, NY 2 awards for 1/78-12/79 1/80-12/81, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Nassau County, NY spusrs 3 agreements 77-82, 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Nassau County, NY 1 arbitration award. 1980 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - New Rochelle, NY 4 arbitration awards. 7/74-12/75 1/76-12/77 1/78-12/79, 1974-1979 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - New Rochelle, NY 2 agreements 1/78-12/82, 1978-1982 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - New York, New York 3 arbitration awards. 1975,76,77, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New York, New York 3 patrol agreement 76-82 1 sgt. agreement 80-82 1 detective agreement 80-82, 1976-1982 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Newburgh, NY 1 arbitration award 1/78-12/79, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Newburgh, NY 2 agreements 1980-84, 1980-1984 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Niagara Falls, NY 2 awards 1/76-12/76 1/79-12/80, 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Niagara Falls, NY 4 agreements 1/76-12/82, 1976-1982 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - North Tonawanda, New York 4 agreements 1973-82, 1973-1982 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - North Tonawanda, New York 1 arbitration Award 1977 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Port Chester, NY 1 arbitration award 4/76-3/77, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Port Chester, NY 2 agreements 4/79-3/81, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Poughkeepsie, NY 2 arbitration awards 1/75-12/75 1/81-12/82, 1975-1982 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Poughkeepsie, NY 2 agreements 1/77-12/80, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Rochester, NY - Midwest City, OK (Box 15)
  - Rochester, New York 3 agreements 1974-76 1978-80, 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rochester, New York 3 arbitration awards for 75-80 agreements, 1975-1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Rockville Centre, NY arbitration award 1/78-12/78, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Rockville Centre, NY 2 agreements 1/79-12/82, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Rome, NY 2 agreements 1/80-12/82, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady, NY 2 agreements 1/78-12/82, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Schenectady, NY 1 arbitration award 1/81-12/82, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Syracuse, New York 3 agreements 1975-76 1977-78 1979-80, 1975-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Syracuse, New York 4 arbitration awards 1975,77,79,81, 1975-1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Troy, New York 3 agreements 1975-76; 1979; 1980-81 see arbitration file for 77-78 agreement., 1975-1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Troy, New York 1 arbitration award. -- 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Utica, New York 4 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Watertown, NY 2 agreements 7/81-6/83, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - White Plains, New York 4 agreements; 2 arbitration awards, 1970-1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - White Plains, New York 2 arbitration awards -- 1975, 1976 See Contract File (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Yonkers, New York 4 agreements 1974-82 period 3 arbitration awards, 1974-1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Akron, Ohio 4 agreements 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Cincinnati, Ohio 2 agreements 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Cleveland, OH 1 agreement 81-83, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland Heights, Ohio 2 memoranda of understanding 1979-81; 1981-83, 1979-1983 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Columbus, Ohio 3 agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Cuyahoga Falls, OHIO 4 agreements 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Dayton, Ohio 5 agreements 1974-82 period, 1974-1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Elyria, OH 3 patrol agreements 76-82, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Fairburn, Ohio 2 memoranda 2 agreements, 1975-1984 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Hamilton, Ohio 4 agreements 1976-84, 1976-1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Findlay, Ohio 1 agreement 1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Kent, Ohio 3 agreements 1 ordinance, 1975-1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Kettering, Ohio agreements, 1976-1984 (Box 15, Folder 29)